A Guide to the Webb-Smith Family Papers, 1703-1929
Library of Virginia
- Court Records (Box 6-10, Reel 2704-2708)
  - Clerks' Fee Bills
    - General Court
      - 1794 (Box 9, Folder 6, Reel 2707)
      - 1805 (Box 9, Folder 7, Reel 2707)
      - 1811 (Box 9, Folder 8, Reel 2707)
    - High Court of Chancery
      - 1792 (Box 9, Folder 9, Reel 2707)
      - 1794 (Box 9, Folder 10, Reel 2707)
      - 1795 (Box 9, Folder 11, Reel 2707)
      - 1797 (Box 9, Folder 12, Reel 2707)
      - 1800 (Box 9, Folder 13, Reel 2707)
    - Superior Court of Chancery, Fredericksburg District, 1826 (Box 9, Folder 14, Reel 2707)
    - Superior Court of Chancery, Richmond District
      - 1815 (Box 9, Folder 15, Reel 2707)
      - 1816 (Box 9, Folder 16, Reel 2707)
      - 1818 (Box 9, Folder 17, Reel 2707)
      - 1819 (Box 9, Folder 18, Reel 2707)
      - 1820 (Box 9, Folder 19, Reel 2707)
      - 1823 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Superior Court of Chancery, Williamsburg District
      - 1815 (Box 9, Folder 21, Reel 2707)
      - 1816 (Box 9, Folder 22, Reel 2707)
    - Amelia County Court
      - 1785 (Box 9, Folder 23, Reel 2707)
      - 1786 (Box 9, Folder 24, Reel 2707)
      - 1787 (Box 9, Folder 25, Reel 2707)
      - 1788 (Box 9, Folder 26, Reel 2707)
      - 1792 (Box 9, Folder 27, Reel 2707)
      - 1799 (Box 9, Folder 28, Reel 2707)
      - n.d. (Box 9, Folder 29, Reel 2707)
    - Essex County Court
      - 1750 (Box 9, Folder 30, Reel 2707)
      - 1764 (Box 9, Folder 31, Reel 2707)
      - 1765 (Box 9, Folder 32, Reel 2707)
      - 1768 (Box 9, Folder 33, Reel 2707)
      - 1772 (Box 9, Folder 34, Reel 2707)
      - 1773 (Box 9, Folder 35, Reel 2707)
      - 1784 (Box 9, Folder 36, Reel 2707)
      - 1785 (Box 9, Folder 37, Reel 2707)
      - 1786 (Box 9, Folder 38, Reel 2707)
      - 1789 (Box 9, Folder 39, Reel 2707)
      - 1791 (Box 9, Folder 40, Reel 2707)
      - 1792 (Box 9, Folder 41, Reel 2707)
      - 1793 (Box 9, Folder 42, Reel 2707)
      - 1794 (Box 9, Folder 43, Reel 2707)
      - 1795 (Box 9, Folder 44, Reel 2707)
      - 1796 (Box 9, Folder 45, Reel 2707)
      - 1797 (Box 9, Folder 46, Reel 2707)
      - 1798 (Box 9, Folder 47, Reel 2707)
      - 1800 (Box 9, Folder 48, Reel 2707)
      - 1801 (Box 9, Folder 49, Reel 2707)
      - 1802 (Box 9, Folder 50, Reel 2707)
      - 1803 (Box 9, Folder 51, Reel 2707)
      - 1804 (Box 9, Folder 52, Reel 2707)
      - 1805 (Box 9, Folder 53, Reel 2707)
      - 1806 (Box 9, Folder 54, Reel 2707)
      - 1807 (Box 9, Folder 55, Reel 2707)
      - 1808 (Box 9, Folder 56, Reel 2707)
      - 1809 (Box 9, Folder 57, Reel 2707)
      - 1810 (Box 9, Folder 58, Reel 2707)
      - 1812 (Box 9, Folder 59, Reel 2707)
      - 1813 (Box 9, Folder 60, Reel 2707)
      - 1814 (Box 9, Folder 61, Reel 2707)
      - 1818 (Box 9, Folder 62, Reel 2707)
      - 1819 (Box 9, Folder 63, Reel 2707)
      - 1825 (Box 9, Folder 64, Reel 2707)
      - 1830 (Box 9, Folder 65, Reel 2707)
    - Essex County Superior Court
      - 1820 (Box 9, Folder 66, Reel 2707)
      - 1825 (Box 9, Folder 67, Reel 2707)
    - Hanover County Court
      - 1788 (Box 9, Folder 68, Reel 2707)
      - 1789 (Box 9, Folder 69, Reel 2707)
      - 1792 (Box 9, Folder 70, Reel 2707)
    - Henrico County Court
      - 1784 (Box 9, Folder 71, Reel 2707)
      - 1785 (Box 9, Folder 72, Reel 2707)
      - 1788 (Box 9, Folder 73, Reel 2707)
    - King and Queen County Court
      - 1768 (Box 9, Folder 74, Reel 2707)
      - 1787 (Box 9, Folder 75, Reel 2707)
      - 1788 (Box 9, Folder 76, Reel 2707)
      - 1789 (Box 9, Folder 77, Reel 2707)
      - 1790 (Box 9, Folder 78, Reel 2707)
      - 1791 (Box 9, Folder 79, Reel 2707)
      - 1792 (Box 9, Folder 80, Reel 2707)
      - 1793 (Box 9, Folder 81, Reel 2707)
      - 1794 (Box 9, Folder 82, Reel 2707)
      - 1795 (Box 9, Folder 83, Reel 2707)
      - 1796 (Box 9, Folder 84, Reel 2707)
      - 1797 (Box 9, Folder 85, Reel 2707)
      - 1798 (Box 9, Folder 86, Reel 2707)
      - 1799 (Box 9, Folder 87, Reel 2707)
      - 1800 (Box 9, Folder 88, Reel 2707)
      - 1801 (Box 9, Folder 89, Reel 2707)
      - 1803 (Box 9, Folder 90, Reel 2707)
      - 1805 (Box 9, Folder 91, Reel 2707)
      - 1811 (Box 9, Folder 92, Reel 2707)
      - 1819 (Box 9, Folder 93, Reel 2707)
      - 1826 (Box 9, Folder 94, Reel 2707)
      - 1837 (Box 9, Folder 95, Reel 2707)
      - 1877 (Box 9, Folder 96, Reel 2707)
    - District Court, King and Queen County (see also Oversize)
      - 1790 (Box 9, Folder 97, Reel 2707)
      - 1791 (Box 9, Folder 98, Reel 2707)
      - 1794 (Box 9, Folder 99, Reel 2707)
      - 1795 (Box 9, Folder 100, Reel 2707)
      - 1796 (Box 9, Folder 101, Reel 2707)
      - 1797 (Box 9, Folder 102, Reel 2707)
      - 1798 (Box 9, Folder 103, Reel 2707)
      - 1799 (Box 9, Folder 104, Reel 2707)
      - 1800 (Box 9, Folder 105, Reel 2707)
      - 1801 (Box 9, Folder 106, Reel 2707)
      - 1802 (Box 9, Folder 107, Reel 2707)
      - 1803 (Box 9, Folder 108, Reel 2707)
      - 1805 (Box 9, Folder 109, Reel 2707)
      - 1807 (Box 9, Folder 110, Reel 2707)
      - 1825 (Box 9, Folder 111, Reel 2707)
      - 1827 (Box 9, Folder 112, Reel 2707)
    - King William County Court
      - 1804 (Box 10, Folder 1, Reel 2708)
      - 1805 (Box 10, Folder 2, Reel 2708)
      - 1813 (Box 10, Folder 3, Reel 2708)
      - 1815 (Box 10, Folder 4, Reel 2708)
      - 1821 (Box 10, Folder 5, Reel 2708)
      - 1822 (Box 10, Folder 6, Reel 2708)
    - King William County Superior Court, 1821 (Box 10, Folder 7, Reel 2708)
    - Lunenburg County Court, 1765 (Box 10, Folder 7a, Reel 2708)
    - Mecklenburg County Court, 1785 (Box 10, Folder 8, Reel 2708)
    - Middlesex County
      - 1786 (Box 10, Folder 9, Reel 2708)
      - 1788 (Box 10, Folder 10, Reel 2708)
      - 1795 (Box 10, Folder 11, Reel 2708)
      - 1798 (Box 10, Folder 12, Reel 2708)
      - 1799 (Box 10, Folder 13, Reel 2708)
      - 1803 (Box 10, Folder 14, Reel 2708)
    - Montgomery County Court, 1785 (Box 10, Folder 15, Reel 2708)
    - Nottoway County Court
      - 1789 (Box 10, Folder 16, Reel 2708)
      - 1790 (Box 10, Folder 17, Reel 2708)
      - 1791 (Box 10, Folder 18, Reel 2708)
      - 1792 (Box 10, Folder 19, Reel 2708)
      - 1793 (Box 10, Folder 20, Reel 2708)
      - 1794 (Box 10, Folder 21, Reel 2708)
    - Richmond Hustings Court, 1787 (Box 10, Folder 22, Reel 2708)
    - Richmond District Court, 1799 (Box 10, Folder 23, Reel 2708)
    - Westmoreland County Court, 1796 (Box 10, Folder 24, Reel 2708)
  - Sheriffs' Fee Bills
    - Caroline County, 1799 (Box 10, Folder 25, Reel 2708)
    - Essex County
      - 1757 (Box 10, Folder 26, Reel 2708)
      - 1764 (Box 10, Folder 27, Reel 2708)
      - 1765 (Box 10, Folder 28, Reel 2708)
      - 1773 (Box 10, Folder 29, Reel 2708)
      - 1790 (Box 10, Folder 30, Reel 2708)
      - 1791 (Box 10, Folder 31, Reel 2708)
      - 1793 (Box 10, Folder 32, Reel 2708)
      - 1794 (Box 10, Folder 33, Reel 2708)
      - 1796 (Box 10, Folder 34, Reel 2708)
      - 1797 (Box 10, Folder 35, Reel 2708)
      - 1798 (Box 10, Folder 36, Reel 2708)
      - 1799 (Box 10, Folder 37, Reel 2708)
      - 1800 (Box 10, Folder 38, Reel 2708)
      - 1801 (Box 10, Folder 39, Reel 2708)
      - 1802 (Box 10, Folder 40, Reel 2708)
      - 1803 (Box 10, Folder 41, Reel 2708)
      - 1809 (Box 10, Folder 42, Reel 2708)
      - 1811 (Box 10, Folder 43, Reel 2708)
      - 1812 (Box 10, Folder 44, Reel 2708)
      - 1819 (Box 10, Folder 45, Reel 2708)
      - 1833 (Box 10, Folder 46, Reel 2708)
    - King and Queen County
      - 1787 (Box 10, Folder 47, Reel 2708)
      - 1788 (Box 10, Folder 48, Reel 2708)
      - 1796 (Box 10, Folder 49, Reel 2708)
      - 1797 (Box 10, Folder 50, Reel 2708)
      - 1798 (Box 10, Folder 51, Reel 2708)
      - 1799 (Box 10, Folder 52, Reel 2708)
      - 1800 (Box 10, Folder 53, Reel 2708)
      - 1801 (Box 10, Folder 54, Reel 2708)
      - 1802 (Box 10, Folder 55, Reel 2708)
      - 1803 (Box 10, Folder 56, Reel 2708)
      - 1804 (Box 10, Folder 57, Reel 2708)
      - 1805 (Box 10, Folder 58, Reel 2708)
      - 1806 (Box 10, Folder 59, Reel 2708)
      - 1808 (Box 10, Folder 60, Reel 2708)
      - 1810 (Box 10, Folder 61, Reel 2708)
      - 1812 (Box 10, Folder 62, Reel 2708)
      - 1818 (Box 10, Folder 63, Reel 2708)
      - 1819 (Box 10, Folder 64, Reel 2708)
      - 1820 (Box 10, Folder 65, Reel 2708)
      - 1827 (Box 10, Folder 66, Reel 2708)
      - 1828 (Box 10, Folder 67, Reel 2708)
      - 1874 (Box 10, Folder 68, Reel 2708)
    - King William County
      - 1798 (Box 10, Folder 69, Reel 2708)
      - 1799 (Box 10, Folder 70, Reel 2708)
      - 1801 (Box 10, Folder 71, Reel 2708)
      - 1802 (Box 10, Folder 72, Reel 2708)
      - 1803 (Box 10, Folder 73, Reel 2708)
      - 1804 (Box 10, Folder 74, Reel 2708)
      - 1805 (Box 10, Folder 75, Reel 2708)
      - 1821 (Box 10, Folder 76, Reel 2708)
      - 1822 (Box 10, Folder 77, Reel 2708)
      - 1823 (Box 10, Folder 78, Reel 2708)
      - 1824 (Box 10, Folder 79, Reel 2708)
      - 1826 (Box 10, Folder 80, Reel 2708)
    - Middlesex County
      - 1786 (Box 10, Folder 81, Reel 2708)
      - 1796 (Box 10, Folder 82, Reel 2708)
      - 1797 (Box 10, Folder 83, Reel 2708)
      - 1799 (Box 10, Folder 84, Reel 2708)
      - 1800 (Box 10, Folder 85, Reel 2708)
      - 1803 (Box 10, Folder 86, Reel 2708)
    - Richmond County, 1800 (Box 10, Folder 87, Reel 2708)
    - Unidentified (Box 10, Folder 88, Reel 2708)
- Estate Papers (see also Oversize) (Box 11-12, Reel 2708-2710)
  - Banks, Robert
    - Accounts (Box 11, Folder 1, Reel 2708)
    - Bonds and Promissory Notes (Box 11, Folder 2, Reel 2708)
    - Clerk's Fee Bills (Box 11, Folder 3, Reel 2708)
    - Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 4, Reel 2708)
    - Executions (Box 11, Folder 5, Reel 2708)
    - Inventory and Appraisement (Box 11, Folder 6, Reel 2708)
    - Receipts (Box 11, Folder 7, Reel 2708)
    - Sheriff's Fee Bills (Box 11, Folder 8, Reel 2708)
    - Suit Papers (Box 11, Folder 9, Reel 2708)
    - Tax Receipts (Box 11, Folder 10, Reel 2708)
    - Sales (Box 11, Folder 11, Reel 2708)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 12, Reel 2708)
  - Brinzendine, Francis (Box 11, Folder 13, Reel 2708)
  - Bush, Bilby (Box 11, Folder 14, Reel 2708)
  - Campbell, Hugh
    - Accounts (Box 11, Folder 15-16, Reel 2708)
    - Bonds and Promissory Notes (Box 11, Folder 17, Reel 2708)
    - Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 17a, Reel 2708)
    - Executions (Box 11, Folder 18, Reel 2708)
    - Judgment Extracts (Box 11, Folder 19, Reel 2708)
    - Receipts (Box 11, Folder 20, Reel 2708)
    - Sheriff's Fee Bills (Box 11, Folder 21, Reel 2708)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 22, Reel 2708)
  - Campbell, James
    - Accounts (Box 11, Folder 23, Reel 2708)
    - Clerk's Fee Bills (Box 11, Folder 24, Reel 2709)
    - Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 25, Reel 2709)
    - Receipts (Box 11, Folder 26, Reel 2709)
    - Suit Papers (Box 11, Folder 27, Reel 2709)
    - Will (copy) (Box 11, Folder 28, Reel 2709)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 29, Reel 2709)
  - Campbell, Peter T. (Box 11, Folder 30, Reel 2709)
  - Campbell, Sarah
    - Accounts (Box 11, Folder 31, Reel 2709)
    - Appraisement of King William Property (Box 11, Folder 32, Reel 2709)
    - Bonds and Promissory Notes (Box 11, Folder 33, Reel 2709)
    - Clerk's Fee Bills (Box 11, Folder 34, Reel 2709)
    - Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 35, Reel 2709)
    - Inventory and Appraisement (Box 11, Folder 36, Reel 2709)
    - Receipts (Box 11, Folder 37, Reel 2709)
    - Sales (Box 11, Folder 38, Reel 2709)
    - Sheriff's Fee Bills (Box 11, Folder 39, Reel 2709)
    - Suit Papers (Box 11, Folder 40, Reel 2709)
    - Tax Receipts (Box 11, Folder 41, Reel 2709)
    - Wills, 1794, 1796 (Box 11, Folder 42, Reel 2709)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 43, Reel 2709)
  - Cauthorn, Henry (Box 11, Folder 44, Reel 2709)
  - Crutcher, Henry (Box 11, Folder 45, Reel 2709)
  - Dickerson, John (Box 11, Folder 46, Reel 2709)
  - Edmondson, John (d. ca. 1773) (Box 12, Folder 1, Reel 2709 or 2710)
  - Edmondson, John (d. ca. 1789) (Box 12, Folder 2, Reel 2709 or 2710)
  - Edmondson, Thomas (Box 12, Folder 3, Reel 2709 or 2710)
  - Emerson, James (Box 12, Folder 4, Reel 2709 or 2710)
  - Evans, William (Box 12, Folder 5, Reel 2709 or 2710)
  - Ferguson, Titus (Box 12, Folder 6, Reel 2709 or 2710)
  - Hawkins, Thomas (Box 12, Folder 7, Reel 2709 or 2710)
  - Hill, Leonard (Box 12, Folder 8, Reel 2709 or 2710)
  - Holmes, Isaac (Box 12, Folder 9, Reel 2709 or 2710)
  - Hoskins, William (Box 12, Folder 10, Reel 2709 or 2710)
  - Mann, Robert
    - Accounts (Box 12, Folder 11, Reel 2709 or 2710)
    - Clerk's Fee Bills (Box 12, Folder 12, Reel 2709 or 2710)
    - Final Account Settlement (Box 12, Folder 13, Reel 2709 or 2710)
    - Inventory and Appraisement (Box 12, Folder 14, Reel 2710)
    - Receipts (Box 12, Folder 15, Reel 2710)
    - Sheriff's Fee Bills (Box 12, Folder 16, Reel 2710)
    - Suit Papers (Box 12, Folder 17, Reel 2710)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 18, Reel 2710)
  - Minter, John (Box 12, Folder 19, Reel 2710)
  - Minter, Philip (Box 12, Folder 20, Reel 2710)
  - Mitchell, Ralph (Box 12, Folder 21, Reel 2710)
  - Montague, James (Box 12, Folder 22, Reel 2710)
  - Munford, Robert (Box 12, Folder 23, Reel 2710)
  - Philips, John (Box 12, Folder 24, Reel 2710)
  - Pollard, William (Box 12, Folder 25, Reel 2710)
  - Pottie, George
    - Accounts (Box 12, Folder 26, Reel 2710)
    - Correspondence (Box 12, Folder 27, Reel 2710)
    - Clerk's Fee Bills, This folder was inadvertently missed in microfilming. Please use originals. (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Deeds, This folder was inadvertently missed in microfilming. Please use originals. (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Receipts, This folder was inadvertently missed in microfilming. Please use originals. (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous, This folder was inadvertently missed in microfilming. Please use originals. (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Ritchie, Archibald, This folder was inadvertently missed in microfilming. Please use originals. (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Seayres, John, This folder was inadvertently missed in microfilming. Please use originals. (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Skelton, John, This folder was inadvertently missed in microfilming. Please use originals. (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Smith, James
    - Accounts, This folder was inadvertently missed in microfilming. Please use originals. (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Bonds, This folder was inadvertently missed in microfilming. Please use originals. (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Clerk's Fees, This folder was inadvertently missed in microfilming. Please use originals. (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Receipts, This folder was inadvertently missed in microfilming. Please use originals. (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Tax Receipts, This folder was inadvertently missed in microfilming. Please use originals. (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Smith, James W., This folder was inadvertently missed in microfilming. Please use originals. (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Smith, Meriwether, This folder was inadvertently missed in microfilming. Please use originals. (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Smith, Thomas, This folder was inadvertently missed in microfilming. Please use originals. (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Stevens, John, This folder was inadvertently missed in microfilming. Please use originals. (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Tyler, Richard, This folder was inadvertently missed in microfilming. Please use originals. (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Webb, Isaac, This folder was inadvertently missed in microfilming. Please use originals. (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Webb, James (d. 1771), This folder was inadvertently missed in microfilming. Please use originals. (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Webb, James (d. 1832), This folder was inadvertently missed in microfilming. Please use originals. (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Webb, Mary, This folder was inadvertently missed in microfilming. Please use originals. (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Webb, William, This folder was inadvertently missed in microfilming. Please use originals. (Box 12, Folder 49)
- Wills (see also Oversize) (Box 13, Reel 2711)
  - Essex County
    - Dickerson, John (Box 13, Folder 1, Reel 2711)
    - Edmondson, Elizabeth (Box 13, Folder 2, Reel 2711)
    - Edmondson, James (Box 13, Folder 3, Reel 2711)
    - Evans, Greenslee (Box 13, Folder 4, Reel 2711)
    - Evans, John (Box 13, Folder 5, Reel 2711)
    - Mann, Robert (Box 13, Folder 6, Reel 2711)
    - Rouzee, Richard (Box 13, Folder 7, Reel 2711)
    - Webb, Mary (Box 13, Folder 8, Reel 2711)
    - Webb, Thomas (Box 13, Folder 9, Reel 2711)
  - King and Queen County
    - Campbell, Alexander (Box 13, Folder 10, Reel 2711)
    - Carlton, Lewis (Box 13, Folder 11, Reel 2711)
    - Fauntleroy, Samuel G. (Box 13, Folder 12, Reel 2711)
    - Fleet, Christopher B. (portion) (Box 13, Folder 13, Reel 2711)
    - Row, Wilson (Box 13, Folder 14, Reel 2711)
  - Middlesex County
    - Chowning, William (Box 13, Folder 15, Reel 2711)
    - Churchill, Sarah (Box 13, Folder 16, Reel 2711)
- Accounts (see also Oversize) (Box 14-15, Reel 2711-2713)
  - 1750-1805 (Box 14, Folder 1-52, Reel 2711-2712)
  - 1806-1900, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 1-57, Reel 2712-2713)
- Receipts (Box 16-17, Reel 2713-2714)
  - 1737-1866 (Box 16, Folder 1-90, Reel 2713-2714)
  - 1871-1929, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 1-19, Reel 2714)
  - Orders for Payment or Goods, 1745-1882 (Box 17, Folder 20-64, Reel 2714)
- Subject Files (Box 18-19, Reel 2714-2716)
  - Act to Amend an Act for Appointing Electors to Choose a President and Vice-President of the United States, 1804 (Box 18, Folder 1, Reel 2714)
  - Act to Incorporate West Point Land Company, 1856 (Box 18, Folder 2, Reel 2714)
  - Act to Regulate the Time and Manner of Administering Certain Oaths, 1789 (Box 18, Folder 3, Reel 2714)
  - Advertisements of Land for Sale, 1824, 1826, 1840 (Box 18, Folder 4, Reel 2714)
  - Affidavits (see also Oversize) (Box 18, Folder 5, Reel 2714)
  - Agreements, 1770-1819 (Box 18, Folder 6, Reel 2714)
  - Agreements, 1820-1880 (Box 18, Folder 7, Reel 2715)
  - Appointment, 1877 (Box 18, Folder 8, Reel 2715)
  - Assignments (Box 18, Folder 9, Reel 2715)
  - Bills of Lading (see also Oversize) (Box 18, Folder 10, Reel 2715)
  - Bills of Sale (Box 18, Folder 11, Reel 2715)
  - Bonds (see also Oversize), 1739-1879 (Box 18, Folder 12-14, Reel 2715)
  - Bounty Land of John Fleet - Receipt, 1798 (Box 18, Folder 15, Reel 2715)
  - Bounty Land of James Holt - Receipt, 1798 (Box 18, Folder 16, Reel 2715)
  - Building Specifications (Box 18, Folder 17, Reel 2715)
  - Cancelled Check, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 18, Reel 2715)
  - Capias (Box 18, Folder 19, Reel 2715)
  - Certificate of Guardianship, 1794 (Box 18, Folder 20, Reel 2715)
  - Certificate re: Quality of Land in Georgia, 1790 (Box 18, Folder 21, Reel 2715)
  - Commission to Examine Witnesses, 1800 (Box 18, Folder 22, Reel 2715)
  - Commissions, 1808, 1810 (Box 18, Folder 23, Reel 2715)
  - Deeds (see also Oversize), 1703-1908 (Box 18, Folder 24-26, Reel 2715)
  - Depositions (Box 18, Folder 27, Reel 2715)
  - Escape Warrant, 1802 (Box 18, Folder 28, Reel 2715)
  - Estate Sales Book - unidentified (Box 18, Folder 29, Reel 2715)
  - Fifas, 1784-1838 (Box 18, Folder 30-31, Reel 2715)
  - Guardian's Accounts
    - Sarah Ellen Smith (Box 19, Folder 1, Reel 2715)
    - William T. Smith (Box 19, Folder 2, Reel 2715)
    - William Webb (Box 19, Folder 3, Reel 2715)
  - Insolvents (Box 19, Folder 4, Reel 2715)
  - Inventories - unidentified (Box 19, Folder 5, Reel 2715)
  - Issue and Chancery Dockets (Box 19, Folder 6, Reel 2715)
  - Letter of Dismissal
    - Calvary Baptist Church, Caroline County, 1852 (Box 19, Folder 7, Reel 2715)
    - Enon Baptist Church, Essex County, 1844 (Box 19, Folder 8, Reel 2715)
    - Upper King and Queen Baptist Church, 1848 (Box 19, Folder 9, Reel 2715)
  - Levies - Overseers of the Poor, King and Queen County, 1838 (Box 19, Folder 10, Reel 2715)
  - License Application, 1891 (Box 19, Folder 11, Reel 2715)
  - List of Negroes of Elira Churchill Derby, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 12, Reel 2715)
  - List of Slave Births, 1743-1797 (Box 19, Folder 12a, Reel 2715)
  - Memoranda (Box 19, Folder 13-15, Reel 2716)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 16, Reel 2716)
  - Money Orders (Box 19, Folder 17, Reel 2716)
  - Numeration Table, 176[?] (Box 19, Folder 18, Reel 2716)
  - Opinions (Box 19, Folder 19, Reel 2716)
  - Orders for Payment of Witnesses, 1762 (Box 19, Folder 20, Reel 2716)
  - Petition to Elect John G. Dew as King and Queen County Court Judge, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 21, Reel 2716)
  - Piscataway Mills Accounts (Box 19, Folder 22, Reel 2716)
  - Powers of Attorney (see also Oversize), 1787-1841 (Box 19, Folder 23, Reel 2716)
  - Promissory Notes, 1765-1925 (Box 19, Folder 24-25, Reel 2716)
  - Proposals for Publishing by Subscription, Mathew Cary, Philadelphia, 1802 (Box 19, Folder 26, Reel 2716)
  - Relinquishment, 1818 (Box 19, Folder 27, Reel 2716)
  - Sheriff's Bond, 1796 (Box 19, Folder 28, Reel 2716)
  - Summons (Box 19, Folder 29, Reel 2716)
  - Surveys (Box 19, Folder 30, Reel 2716)
  - Tax Receipts, 1741-1897 (Box 19, Folder 31-32, Reel 2716)
  - Tobacco Inspector Bonds, 1784-1785 (Box 19, Folder 33, Reel 2716)
- Account Books, Fee Books, Memorandum Books, and Ledgers (Box 20-22, Reel 2716-2718)
  - Account Books
    - 1783-1790 (Box 20, Folder 1, Reel 2716)
    - 1785-1790 (Box 20, Folder 2, Reel 2716)
    - 1787-1789 (Box 20, Folder 3, Reel 2716)
    - General Expenses, 1805-1808 (Box 20, Folder 4, Reel 2716)
    - 1867-1878 (Box 20, Folder 5, Reel 2716)
    - n.d. (Box 20, Folder 6, Reel 2716)
  - Fee Books
    - 1786 (Box 20, Folder 7, Reel 2716)
    - 1787 (Box 20, Folder 8, Reel 2716)
    - 1789 (Box 20, Folder 9, Reel 2716)
  - Ledgers
    - A (Box 20, Folder 10-18, Reel 2716-2717)
    - B (Box 21, Folder 1-8, Reel 2717)
    - C (Box 21, Folder 9, Reel 2718)
    - L (Box 21, Folder 10, Reel 2718)
    - M - Index (Box 21, Folder 11, Reel 2718)
  - Memorandum Books
    - 1769-1776 (Box 22, Folder 1, Reel 2718)
    - Memorandum and Account Book, Piscataway Mills, 1781-1784 (Box 22, Folder 2, Reel 2718)
    - 1781-1790 (Box 22, Folder 3, Reel 2718)
    - 1791- December 1794 (Box 22, Folder 4, Reel 2718)
    - 1791-1798 (Box 22, Folder 5, Reel 2718)
    - May 1792 - May 1797 (Box 22, Folder 6, Reel 2718)
    - December 1794 - February 1796 (Box 22, Folder 7, Reel 2718)
    - February 1796 - June 1797 (Box 22, Folder 8, Reel 2718)
    - June 1797 - June 1798 (Box 22, Folder 9, Reel 2718)
    - June 1798 - February 1801 (Box 22, Folder 10, Reel 2718)
    - 1807-1807 (Box 22, Folder 11, Reel 2718)
    - July 1807 - January 1812 (Box 22, Folder 12, Reel 2718)
  - Store Journal A, King and Queen County, 1792-1793 (Box 22, Folder 13, Reel 2718)
- Oversize (Box 23, Reel 2719)
  - Accounts (Box 23, Folder 1, Reel 2719)
  - Affidavit of William Coleman, 1816 (Box 23, Folder 2, Reel 2719)
  - Bills of Lading (Box 23, Folder 3, Reel 2719)
  - Bonds (Box 23, Folder 4, Reel 2719)
  - Clerk's Fee Bills, King and Queen County District Court (Box 23, Folder 5, Reel 2719)
  - Deeds (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Estate of Hugh Campbell - Account (Box 23, Folder 7, Reel 2719)
  - Estate of Hugh Campbell - Clerk's Fee Bill (Box 23, Folder 8, Reel 2719)
  - Estate of James Campbell
    - Accounts (Box 23, Folder 9, Reel 2719)
    - Inventory and appraisement, 1774 (Box 23, Folder 10, Reel 2719)
  - Estate of James Montague - Appraisement, 1782 (Box 23, Folder 11, Reel 2719)
  - Estate of James Smith - Accounts (Box 23, Folder 12, Reel 2719)
  - Estate of Richard Tyler - Sales, 1761 (Box 23, Folder 13, Reel 2719)
  - Letter, 1797, and cover, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 14, Reel 2719)
  - List of Militia Certificates, 1785, and Muster Roll, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 15, Reel 2719)